Hello friends welcome to
Chan sep
insur
mut
[Applause]
fund
C clear
only hospit
Hospital
after hospit home treatment at home for
three or more days due to Patient
condition or unability of Hospital
bir expens living hospit for donating
or up to 5 for emergency transfer air
ambulance
additional coverage up to 30,000 for up
to two deliveries or lawful termination
of pregancy after 3
expenses up to 10,000 for within 90 days
of
of alcoholism or drug or substance
abuse
claim except
for Tempo plastic any type of Pops
fibroid
your nearest Navy Network Hospital find
network
Hospital go to the insurance help and
provide the
followings
[Music]
will the status of your claim and your
bill will be settled in less than 4 Hour
Maxim if
approved relationship
[Music]
manager
nor
for deps
for
bye